https://nzarchaeology.org/membership/privacy-statement

Membership Privacy Statement - NZ Archaeological Association
LOGIN
needy young amateur japan babe fantastic bukkake on web camera. nude photos
Publications Search
Archaeology in New Zealand (AINZ)
Membership Membership Privacy Statement
Scope:
This statement applies to personal information we collect about our members.
Personal Information:
We do not collect personal information unless you choose to give it to us, for example on your membership request or renewal form or via email.
Use and disclosure:
Personal information, such as names, addresses and email addresses, are held for the purposes of communication with members about New Zealand Archaeological Association matters. This includes, but is not limited to, provision of Archaeology in New Zealand, membership renewal information, communication from Council, Sub-committees or other appointed officers, information regarding NZAA’s annual conference, other NZAA events and news.
We will only use personal information that you provide to us for the purposes for which you supplied it or, in exceptional situations, for other reasons permitted under the Privacy Act 1993.
We only disclose personal information about you on the Consultants Directory if you have made a request in writing or via email.
Names of members who have made donations are acknowledged in Archaeology in New Zealand unless you request to remain anonymous.
We generally do not share your personal information with others unless this is necessary for the purpose for which you gave us the information (for instance to investigate a complaint). Occasionally the law may require us to disclose it (for instance to investigate a criminal offence), or there may be safety reasons for disclosing it.
We may analyse non-identifiable data to improve our services.
Your Rights and Choices:
We are happy to provide you with access to any personal information that we hold about you. If it is wrong, please ask us to correct it. To ask for access and correction, see our contact details.
You can ask to be removed from mailing lists or the Consultant List at any time.
Contact us if you have any questions.
Promoting and fostering archaeological research in New Zealand.
PO Box 6337Dunedin 9059New ZealandContact NZAA »
Latest News
NZAA Representation in Archaeology Panel
Walton Fund 2020 Successful Applicants
What can we learn from ArchSite?
Archaeology Week 2020
Members Update
Subscribe to ENews Receive our E-newsletter with archaeological news and updates:
Click here
Copyright 2017 New Zealand Archaeological Association Inc | All Rights Reserved | Sitemap
Home
About the New Zealand Archaeological Association (NZAA)
Training & Continuing Professional Development (CPD)
Publications
Publications Search
Archaeology in New Zealand (AINZ)
Early Career Research & Publishing Workshops – Annual Conference 2018
